(Sheldon:)Oh no.
- What's the matter?
- I forgot my flash drive.
(Summer:)- So?
- So we have to go back.
Okay, Sheldon, I'm gonna say, "Why?"
(Leonard:)And your answer cannot be
"Because I forgot my flash drive."
(Sheldon:)You don't understand.
(Sheldon:)My flash drive has my paper
on astrophysical probes...
(Sheldon:)...of M-theory effects
in the early universe...
...I was gonna give to George Smoot
at the conference.
(Leonard:)Why do you have to give your paper
to George Smoot?
(Sheldon:)It's brilliant. He needs to read it.
(Leonard:)So you'll send him an email
when we get back.
(Sheldon:)Then I won't get to see
his face light up as he reads it.
- Right. Of course.
- Oh, this is an unmitigated disaster.
(Leonard:)Well, there's nothing you can do about it,
so relax.
(Leonard:)Sit back, enjoy the clickety-clack
of the steel wheels on the polished rails.
[SINGING] You forgot your flash drive
You forgot your flash drive
(Sheldon:)You forgot your flash drive
Only 10 hours, 55 minutes to go.